# Abdulwahab Jimoh

Lagos Mainland, Lagos State, Nigeria

omoniyi.success@gmail.com

+2348188026726

linkedin.com/in/wabjay

## Summary

I'm a front-end developer, I have prioritized refining customer satisfaction in approaches to a host of projects I have overseen, which has, in turn, endeared me to clients. Having devoted my time to science and technology, I recognize the quest of man to use the web as a tool for immense possibilities and I am keen to help actualize the vision. I surely realizes the need for continuous updates, as it is the only constant in the field of technology to provide the best website development experience to my customers.

## **Experience**



### 鍧 Frontend Developer

**Ethco Group Limited** 

Aug 2022 - Present (4 months +)

Building the landing pages, admin web app for helping Ethnic and Independent convenience store owners.

- Converted the Ethco figma landing page to pixel perfect implemented code with full responsiveness using plain HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Worked on Airtable API to receive data from forms.
- · Worked on the ethco admin portal using next.js and ant design use redux for the state management and consume the API created from the backend.

#### Frontend Web Developer

Ownerfi

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022 (2 months)

Developed project with reactjs, built a step form and manage data state with context api. Implement ReactQuill for rich text editor and address autocomplete using google place autocomplete. Used firebase for database stage and user authentication.

## **Website Developer**

Techtank

Jul 2022 - Aug 2022 (2 months)

Designed the landing pages with reactis and implemented form designs to email integration with emailis.

#### Frontend Web Developer

Ayrem

May 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 8 months)

Ayrem is a safe and trustworthy way for africans to purchase crypto, giftcard and dataplans conviniently at unbeatable rates.

Some of my achievements at Ayrem are:

- Convert the Ayrem figma landing page to pixel perfect implemented code with full responsiveness.
- Worked on the ayrem web app design of over 50 pages and converted it using plain HTML, CSS and JavaScript code.
- Consumed the API created backend and implemented it on the Ayrem web app.
- Designed and implemented the Ayrem admin backend office using HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Strategized with the team to implement features to make the website more engaging to the users.

#### Studio and IT Manager

**Eccenticanation productions** 

Feb 2017 - May 2019 (2 years 4 months)

Movie & Music Production, Modelling, Concert Management:

Some of my roles in the organization are:

- To oversee the operation of the music studio.
- Designed and Implement the website with Wordpress CMS.
- Implemented continuous updates on the website.
- Worked on Google business and added the company address on the Map.
- Made some important decisions based feedbacks.
- Worked directly with the PR to create contents for the social media platforms, plan ads and campaigns.

#### **Information Technology Manager**

Convergence Hotels & Suites

Feb 2016 - Jan 2017 (1 year)

Provides accomodation service with exquisite international and local cuisine delicacies.

Some of my achievements as the IT Manager includes:

- Designed and Implement the website with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.
- Created and organize the database of the hotel with Microsoft Excel.
- Developed brand strategy and statistics systems based on feedbacks.

- Created contents and schedule posts for the social media platforms.
- Check and approve bookings on the booking platforms.
- Attended to client complaints from the booking platforms and resolve them.

#### Raphson Web Design Intern

Raphson Systems Technologies Ltd

Oct 2014 - Dec 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Software /web solutions to Nigerian corporate organizations and individuals.

My Achievements working as a web design intern with Raphson Systems Technologies Ltd includes:

- Conceptualizing creative ideas with clients.
- Maintaining, testing and improving the design of the website using Typo3 CMS.
- Tutoring and designing sample pages with HTML and CSS.
- Preparing design plans and presenting the website structure with Adobe Dreamwaver.

#### **Education**

#### kwara state polytechnic

National Diploma, Computer Science 2012 - 2014

#### **Licenses & Certifications**

National Diploma - Kwara State Polytechnic



**G** Fundamental of Digital Marketing - Google

#### Skills

Firebase • Google Places • emailjs-com • ReactQuill • Next.js • Ant Design • Airtable • Redux Thunk • Dreamweaver • Microsoft Office